
Code for ConvEEGNN

P_(participant id)_initial.mat: inital parameters for the best performance

variables inside a P_(participant id)_initial.mat file:
• cnn_setup:  initial weights of the network for every cross-validation
• train_idx:  index of train samples for every cross-validation
• valid_test: index of valid samples for every cross-validation
• test_idx:   index of test samples for every cross-validation
